https://www.wildhuman.com/privacy-policy/

Home / Privacy Policy
Wild Human Privacy Policy
Cookies
Our websites use cookies for the purposes of storing a client’s shopping basket and may be disabled in the client’s own web browser.
Personal Information
Wild Human collects personal information when our clients book a course or expedition, or when subscribing to the Wild Human mailing list. Client information is used for email course information and ensuring client safety, such as relevant medical information and food allergies.
The Wild Human mailing list requires the client to provide an email address to receive regular updates. Users may unsubscribe from the mailing list at any time; the user is sent details of how to unsubscribe when initially signing up.
Any personal information collected will not be disclosed to any other third party, except in the case of cooperating with law enforcement agencies to aid in identifying those persons using our services for illegal activities.
Wild Human is required under UK tax law to keep basic customer personal information (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 6 years after which time it will be destroyed.
At any point customers can request to see their personal information stored by Wild Human.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
E-commerce payment gateway
Our e-commerce provider is Evalon who are PCI compliant. All purchases are encrypted using the Secure Socket Layer standard.
External Links
This website may have links to other websites. Wild Human is not responsible for the privacy practices, actions, or the content of other websites.
